Mohammad Barokatu Rizky

Software Engineer

+62 82144481502

r portofolio.barox.tech

Kabupaten Probolinggo, Jawa Timur

SUMMARY

I am web technology enthusiast. Have experience for web development 3 years. I always learn about website technology. I want to develop my skill for my carrier, and I want make some innovation from web development in order some web system/app can develop and I can manage server for web deployment by linux distro. I am web security enthusiast too, I reconnaize web that have some bug bounty program for wasting my time.

EXPERIENCE

Web Developer 07/2022 - Presen

PT. Adi Media Expertindo

I work full time in this company that have a project using ReactJS and Express JS for their web technology and use Firebase for their database and other service that we need as like firestore, firebase cloud messaging and others.

Remote Web Developer (Part Time)

01/2022 - 03/2023

UKMGO Digital

I have part time work in this start up, usually I work the client project using PHP or Golang for Back-end Technologhy. And using ReactJS for Front-end Technologhy.

System Analyst Specialist (Internship)

09/2022 - 12/2022

Sagara Technology

I work as a system analyst for making project flow and ERD.

Web Developer 04/2021 - 05/2022

CV. Generasi Jaya Kraksaan

I hold 2 position in this company, but I focused in Administration.

and I develop the system website front-end using ReactJS.

Administration Staff 02/2021 - 05/2022

CV. Generasi Jaya Kraksaan

I experienced as administration staff in this company and I have experience in managing archive.

Web Development Teacher 07/2020 - 02/2021

SMK Muhammadiyah 02 Paleran

I teach basic of web developement in this school just in 6 months.

And I made accounting web apps for this school.

Web Developer 05/2019 - 05/2020

PP. Darul Lughah Wal Karomah

First experience of my work in my boarding school, that my teacher give me a chance to become a Web Developer in boarding school.

In this boarding school I have develop some Web Apps for Accounting, and System Administration.

Intership Operator 02/2019 - 04/2019

PT. Paiton Operation and Maintenance Indonesia

I apprentice in PT. POMI because it is school program that I must have to intership in a industry for 2 months.

In this apprenticeship I have experience for operating opertion software like door log database, and make a permittion for some employer to access some door.

EDUCATION

Rekayasa Perangkat Lunak 2020

SMK Darul Lughah Wal Karomah - High School

• 3rd Champion of English Speech Boarding School Competition

CERTIFICATES

Sertifikat WP Pro Course by Niagahoster 05/2022 - Present

Google Analytics for Beginner 10/2020 - Present

Certificate of Recognition (bhinneka.com bug reporting) 06/2020 - Present

Google Digital Marketing 12/2020 - 03/2022

SKILLS

Golang Intermediate Web Penetration Tester Intermediate PHP Web Security Patchman Expert Beginner HTML ReactJS Intermediate Advanced Bootstrap Intermediate Laravel Intermediate

JavaScript Intermediate

LANGUAGES

English Intermediate Arabic Basic

Indonesia Fluent